New York State AFL-CIO Director Al Davidoff Files 6203
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State AFL-CIO Director Al Davidoff Files
1986-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO)
New York State AFL- CIO
Davidoff, Al
6203
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Records.
8258615
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 24, 2006
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6202: New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Files 6202 OH: New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Interviews Oral History on Minidiscs 6202 AV: New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Interviews Audio-Visual Materials 6202 P(d): New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Digital Photographs
Davidoff, Al; New York State AFL-CIO; AFL-CIO
8258615
- Airport Organizing, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- American Federation of Labor Congress of Industrial Organizations, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Alliance For Retired Americans- New York, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Anheuser-Bush, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A. Phillip Randolph Institute-, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Scope and Contents
  The Metropolitan New York Chapter
- Boston Organizing Conference, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bronfenbrenner, Kate, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bronfenbrenner, Kate, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Buffalo Building and Construction Trades Department, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Buffalo Building and Construction Trades Council, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Buffalo, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  News Articles
- Buffalo, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Notes
- Buffalo Organizers Meeting, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Carey, Ron, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Casino Workers- New York, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Central Labor Council- Annual Reports, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Central New York Labor Federation, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Chemung County AFL-CIO Assembly Financial Report, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Child Care Campaign- New York, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Civil Service Employees Union, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Coalition For Economic Justice, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Coalition For Economic Justice, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Congressional Districts- New York, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Committee on Political Education (Counts), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Communications Workers of America, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Contracts, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Contract Campaign Problem #1, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Bronfenbrenner, Kate
- Contract Survey, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Coordinated Bargaining- The Steelworkers' Experience, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Cornell University, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Cornell University Conference- Reviving Unions, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Cortland Standard, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- CVS Corporation, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Davidoff, Al, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Davidoff, Al, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Davidoff, Al, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Davidoff, Al, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  Weekly Report
- Demographics- New York, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Doctors Unions, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Easton, Billy, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Faculty At Work- Labor Support, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Financial Report, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Fletcher, Bill, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Field Mobilization Staff Retreat, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Free Trade of the Americas/ Fast Track, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union- Local 4 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Howard, Julie Dade, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Independent Labor Unions- New York, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Immigration Workers- Organizing, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Industrial Labor and Relations- Cornell University, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Job Positions, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Jones, Pat, 1996-2001 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Keith, Marc, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- King Kullen Strike, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Labor Education, 1993-2003 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Labor-Religion Coalition- New York, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Labor-Religion Coalition- New York, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Lane, Michael Campaign, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Local Labor Councils, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Long Island Federation, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Long Island- Local 424, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Lott Amendment, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Malloy, Ed, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Maps- Albany Troy Schenectady Area, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- McCauley, James (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Memorial Day- Worker's, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Mid-State Central Labor Commission, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- National Coalition Building Institute, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- New Alliance, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- New Alliance- Affiliates, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- New Alliance- American Federation of Government Employees, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- New Alliance- Capital District Labor Council, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- New Alliance- Media, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- New Alliance- New York State United Teachers, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- New Alliance- Subsidy, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- New Alliance- United Food & Commercial International Union, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- New Alliance- United Union of Roofers, Waterproofers, and Allied Workers, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- New Party News, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- New York City- 32B/ Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Coalition (Box 1, Folder 80)
- New York City- Organizing Conference (Box 1, Folder 81)
- New York City- Wall Street, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- New Yorkers For Fiscal Fairness, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- New York State- Laws, 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- New York State Labor-Religion Coalition, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- North American Free Trade Agreement, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Office & Professional Employees, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  International Union Local 153- Group Health Inc. Strike
- Occupational Safety and Health Hazard Abatement Board, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Organizing- Kowalski, Mirija Jane, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Organizing- New York, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Organizing- Training, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Oswego County Labor Council, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Pataki, George- Labor Legislation on New York Indian Nation Casinos, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Paycheck Deception, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Politics, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Press- General, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Public Employees Federation, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Religious Labor Organizations, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Resumes, 1997-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Rivera, Dennis, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Rochester and Genesee Valley Area Labor Federation- AFL-CIO, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Rochester- Labor Council, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Rochester- Union Cities, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Service Employees International Union- 1199, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Service Employees International Union- 1199, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Soviet Movement Unionism, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Speeches, 1986-1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Stanford Organizing Committee (Box 2, Folder 22)
- State Fed- Work plan, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Staten Island Race, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Strategic Research (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Street Heat- Mobilizing To Win, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Steuben County Labor Council, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Student Labor Activities- AFL-CIO, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Syracuse- Greater Syracuse Labor Council, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Syracuse- Greater Syracuse Labor Council- Union Cities, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Teamsters National Black Caucus of New York State, Inc,., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Trade Unions, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Transportation Communications International Union, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Transportation Workers Union- Local 100 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Troy Area Labor Council, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Union City By City- Central Labor Councils, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Union Mergers and Union Revival, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- United Food & Commercial Workers- Local 1, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- United Way, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- United Way, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Union Summer, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- United Steelworkers of America- Eagle Comtronics Campaign, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Upper Hudson Area Central Labor Council, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  Minutes
- Welfare Reform, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Westchester- Putnam Counties Central Labor Body, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Work Plan, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Working Families Party, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Working Women- Child Care, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Worker's Memorial Day- New York City, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Worker's Memorial Day, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Workforce Development System- New York City (Box 2, Folder 53)
- AFL-CIO- Affiliation Letters, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO- Arts and Entertainment Unions (Box 3, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO- Ask a Working Woman Conference, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO- Benefits, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO- Bruno, Joseph, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO- Budget, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO- Calendar of Events, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO- Communications, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO- Community Services, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO- Community Services Network, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO- Constitutional Convention, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO- Constitutional State Federal Constitution (Box 3, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO- Cooperative Organization Campaigns, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO- C.O.P.E. Convention, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO- Directories, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO- Economic Education Project, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO- Ethical Practices Code, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO- Gay/ Lesbian, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO- General Information, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO- Health Care Campaign, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO- Housing Investment Trust, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- AFL-CIO- Human Resources Development Institute, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO- Jobs with Justice, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO- Kaiser Permanente, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO- Labor, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIO- Labor to Neighbor, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO- Management Meeting, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- AFL-CIO- Michael Moore Videos, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- AFL-CIO- Mohonk Retreat (Box 3, Folder 29)
- AFL-CIO- Monthly Plans (Box 3, Folder 30)
- AFL-CIO- Motown, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- AFL-CIO- Organizing Immigrants, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Albany Central Labor Council, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Capital District- Area Labor Federation, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Carpenters, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Central Labor Council- Assessment, Dissolving Procedures, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Common Sense Economics For Working Families, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Energy Policy (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Expense Information, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union- Local 4, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Labor Day, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Membership Education and Mobilization For Organizing, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Membership Education and Mobilization For Organizing, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- New York Central Labor Council, 1997-2002 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- New York State- AFL-CIO, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- New York State Federation, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Buffalo Central Labor Council, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- AFL-CIO- Economic Education, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO- National Day of Action on Workfare/ Welfare, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO- New York Times, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO- News From Other Regions, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO- Northeast Region Staff Meeting, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO- Northeast Region Staff Meeting, 1997-2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO- Organizing, 1997-2002 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO- Organizing Institute, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO- Overhead slides (Box 4, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO- Press, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO- Press/ Media, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO- Regions, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO- Strawberry Campaign, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO- Street Heat, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO- Training, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO- Union Cities, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO- Union Cities, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO- Voice At Work Month, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO- Webpage, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO- Worker's Memorial Day, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO- Working Woman's Campaign, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- AFL- Staff/Leadership Retreat, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- New York State Federation, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Political Program Slides, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Right to Organize, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Sweeney, John J.- Speeches, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Union Community Fund, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- United States Airways Organizing, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Weekly Reports, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Weekly Reports, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- AFL-CIO- Executive Council Meeting, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO- Help Make the Global Economy Work for Working Families Everywhere (Box 5, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO- Northeast Region- (folder 1 of 2), 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO- Northeast Region- (folder 2 of 2), 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Membership Mobilization, Politics and Legislation, Organizing, Coalitions
- Cornell University-Leadership Institute (folder 1 of 3), 2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Cornell University-Leadership Institute (folder 2 of 3), 2001 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Cornell University-Leadership Institute (folder 3 of 3), 2001 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- New York State AFL-CIO/ Cornell Union Leadership Institute (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Notes (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Notes (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Notes (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Rebuilding Unions, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- State Director's Training, (folder 1 of 2), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- State Director's Training, (folder 2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Tompkins County Board of Elections, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Summary. Voter master call list.